http://adventuresport.co.uk/privacy-policy

Hovercraft Experience
Jaguar Land Rover Employee Learning Scheme (ELS)
Your Adventure
Already made a booking?Fetch your adventure details by entering your booking reference below:
Reference:
Corporate Events
Challenge and Champion - Full Day Teambuilding Events in Warwickshire
Tradition & Targets: Country Pursuits (Full-Day)
Speed and Safari - Adrenalin Driving (Full-Day)
Tradition & Targets: Country Pursuits (Half-Day)
Speed & Safari: Adrenalin Driving (Half-Day)
Challenge & Champion: Team-Building (Half-Day)
Activity Suggestions
Group Size:
Budget:
Share This Page
Connect With Us
Follow us, or connect with us, via the social media channels below to get your hands on exclusive offers, photos, videos and more!
Join Adventure Sports On:
Twitter
Facebook
YouTube
This privacy notice sets out how Adventure Sports (Warwickshire) Ltd. (Adventure Sports) uses and protects any information that you give to us when you use this website.
Adventure Sports is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Adventure Sports may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 9th May 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Your name
Email address and telephone number
Information relevant to customer interest in Adventure Sports
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Send you details about the activity / event that you have asked about
Send you a booking confirmation email
Payment confirmation details
Cookies
We do use Google Analytics cookies to anonymously collect website usage data from visitors. It is impossible
to identify an individual with the data collected, and we simply use it to
improve the customer experience of the site. For full details about Google Analytics cookies have a look at Google's technical page (http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.
Personal data is kept for seven years to comply with legal and insurance requirements. After seven years any data held (electronically or paper versions) will be deleted or destroyed.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA) and the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to:
Adventure Sports Ltd., Wedgnock Rifle Range, Wedgnock Lane, Warwick, CV35 7PX.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
You also have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner's Office if you are not happy with how Adventure Sports handles your data.
Legal Disclaimer
Adventure Sports has taken every reasonable step
to ensure the content of these webpages is fully accurate and correct in
every detail however it does not warrant or make any other
representation as to the content, extent or completeness of the
information, text, graphics, links or other items contained in this
website. All information and content found on this website is provided
without any warranties, either express or implied, including, but not
limited to, warranties of title, non-infringement or implied warranties,
other than those warranties which are incapable of exclusion,
restriction or modification under applicable law.
At no stage shall Adventure Sports Ltd. be liable for
any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special or consequential
damages that result from the use of, or inability to use, this website
or from information provided by the website.
This limitation applies whether the alleged liability is based on
contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or any other basis, even if
we have been advised of the possibility of such damage. Because some
jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or
consequential damages, our liability in such jurisdictions shall be
limited to the extent permitted by law.
You may not reproduce any of the materials contained on this website
in any format without prior consent. If you wish to use any of the
materials on this website for republication in any format you must first
apply in writing to:
Adventure Sports (Warwickshire) Ltd. Wedgnock Rifle RangeWedgnock Lane Warwick Warwickshire, CV35 7PX
Jaguar Land Rover Employee Learning Scheme (ELS)
@AdSportsWarwick on Twitter
Fetching tweet…
@AdSportsWarwick
Adventure Sports (Warwickshire) Ltd.
